

### BAYRAM ATAKAN KOSDURMA

## COMPUTER ENGINEERING



atakan.kosdurma@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bursa Technical University

Computer Engineering

2018 - 2023(2.85-4.00)

#### **SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Critical Thinking
- Algorythm Analysis and Design
- Data abstractions
- Object-oriented programming
- Internet applications
- Web Development
- Agile & Scrum
- Debugging

# PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES AND FRAMEWORKS

- Angular
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- C#

#### **ABOUT ME**

I graduated from Bursa Technical University in the area of Computer Engineering in 2023. From my point of view, I think I gained a lot of experience in my license area. I worked as an Intern at Pirahas Yazılım voluntarily. I worked on the Front-End side of the project for 3 months. During my summer internship, I developed an Angular project about scraping data from GitLab and using them to make tables and graphs to see how many commits each person has. And, During my long internship, I worked on a live project called Workouth at the company ASSA Yazılım using Angular with ASP.NET. After that, I worked at Mercury and got a taste of professional work life. I worked there using Angular, Typescript. I also improved myself with remote working, Jira, Agile methodology and Scrum methodology. Before my license education, I was a dancer in high school. With my dance team, we traveled to 16 countries and met many people from different cultures. These travels helped me to improve my communication skills with people. And dancing improved my teamwork, and leadership skills. I am currently dancing at Nilüfer Belediyesi Folk Dance Ensemble. In addition to all of that, I am looking forward to developing myself in my license area by doing projects and gaining work experience. Thank you for your interest.

Regards, Bayram Atakan Koşdurma.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Mercury Technology - Remote - October 2023 - March 2024

• I worked as a Frontend Developer at Mercury. In order to get a hold of the project, I worked with different developers. I honed my Angular, Typescript, CSS, HTML, and teamwork skills during my work time. As a full-stack team, I worked with back-end developers and QA engineers time to time. We were developing a project that helps to track and create shipments. The application is currently used in USA. I can say that I developed my frontend skills there.

#### FRONT-END / BACK-END DEVELOPER - INTERNSHIP

Assa Software & Consultancy - Bursa - October 2022 - January 2023

• To start with Assa Software, company develops web applications and mobile applications just like my other workplaces. I have been given tasks on the ASP.NET Zero framework to learn back-end and front-end development. I worked with the employees and got a taste of professional work life. I used Angular framework in frontend and C# in back-end development.

- Python
- Java
- ASP.NET

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English B2-C1
- German A1

#### **HOBBIES**

- Dance
- Cycling
- Motorsports

#### **ANGULAR DEVELOPER - SUMMER INTERNSHIP**

Codemine Software GmbH. - Bursa - August 2022 / September 2022

• First of all, the company gave me a project. They work with GitLab. Developers commit their work to GitLab to keep the project updated. My project subject is developing an Angular Project that brings the committers with given conditions and prints them to a graphic and table on a web page. I completed the project in 10 work days. For the remaining 10 days of my internship, I worked in their project and resolved issues for them.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER - VOLUNTEER INTERNSHIP

Pirahas Software - Bursa - August 2020 / November 2020

• I started as an intern at Pirahas Software. To get used to the project, I started localizing their texts from Turkish to English. As a result of their Front-End Developer quitting the job, I started working as a Front-End Developer. After school started, I left there to focus on my studying

#### **ACTIVITES AND COMMUNITIES**

- Anadolu Barış Youth and Sports Club Society (2014-2018)
- Bursa Nilüfer Folk Dance Ensemble (2018-Still Going)
- Taekwon-do in different clubs (2007-2013)
- Bursa Technical University Google Developers Students Club (2022-2023)
- Google Developers Group Bursa Core Team Member (November 2022- 2023)

#### **PROFILES**

- https://github.com/bayramatakankosdurma
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bayram-atakan-kosdurma/

#### REFERENCES

Muhammet Akvardar

Eylem Ökcü

Pirahas Software, Çiçek Sepeti, Defacto Mercury Technology QA / Test Engineer